let questions = [
    {
        numb:1,
        question:"Which is the largest country in the world",
        answer:"Russia",
        options:[
            "Russia",
            "Armenia",
            "Georgia",
            "France"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:2,
        question:"Which country has the largest population in the world",
        answer:"India",
        options:[
            "China",
            "India",
            "Libanon",
            "Cameroon"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:3,
        question:"What river flows trough Paris",
        answer:"Seine",
        options:[
            "Thames",
            "Yan Cin",
            "Ninva",
            "Seine"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:4,
        question:"Which capital citys native name is Krung Thep",
        answer:"Thailand",
        options:[
            "Thailand",
            "Dominica",
            "Russia",
            "England"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:5,
        question:"Sakartvelo is the native name of which country",
        answer:"Georgia",
        options:[
            "Arabic Emirates",
            "Georgia",
            "Russia",
            "England"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:6,
        question:"Which two countres have been merged",
        answer:"North and South Korea",
        options:[
            "North and South Korea",
            "Spain and Italy",
            "Brazil and Argentina",
            "Armenia and Georgia"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:7,
        question:"Manchuria is a region of wich country",
        answer:"China",
        options:[
            "India",
            "Georgia",
            "Japan",
            "China"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:8,
        question:"Port Louis is the capital of which country",
        answer:"Mauritius",
        options:[
            "Oman",
            "Somalia",
            "Mauritius",
            "China"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:9,
        question:"Which countrys national color is orange",
        answer:"Netherland",
        options:[
            "Netherland",
            "Somalia",
            "Morocco",
            "Vatikan city"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:10,
        question:"What is the largest US state by area",
        answer:"Alaska",
        options:[
            "Dibed",
            "Forest",
            "Volga",
            "Alaska"
        ]
    }
]

